■
m 240 290 l 240 300 l 250 300 l 250 290 m 250 290 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 210 240 l 210 250 l 220 250 l 220 240 m 220 240 m 260 230 l 260 240 l 270 240 l 270 230 m 270 230 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 40 210 l 40 220 l 50 220 l 50 210 m 50 210 m 280 180 l 280 190 l 290 190 l 290 180 m 290 180 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 50 320 l 50 330 l 60 330 l 60 320 m 60 320 m 190 80 l 190 90 l 200 90 l 200 80 m 200 80 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 320 140 l 320 150 l 330 150 l 330 140 m 330 140 m 100 270 l 100 280 l 110 280 l 110 270 m 110 270 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 130 130 l 130 140 l 140 140 l 140 130 m 140 130 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 280 250 l 280 260 l 290 260 l 290 250 m 290 250 m 290 200 l 290 210 l 300 210 l 300 200 m 300 200 m 190 170 l 190 180 l 200 180 l 200 170 m 200 170 m 60 220 l 60 230 l 70 230 l 70 220 m 70 220 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 70 150 l 70 160 l 80 160 l 80 150 m 80 150 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 80 160 l 80 170 l 90 170 l 90 160 m 90 160 m 320 50 l 320 60 l 330 60 l 330 50 m 330 50 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 200 110 l 200 120 l 210 120 l 210 110 m 210 110 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 240 250 l 240 260 l 250 260 l 250 250 m 250 250 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 270 100 l 270 110 l 280 110 l 280 100 m 280 100 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 150 80 l 150 90 l 160 90 l 160 80 m 160 80 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 290 70 l 290 80 l 300 80 l 300 70 m 300 70 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 70 260 l 70 270 l 80 270 l 80 260 m 80 260 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 240 320 l 240 330 l 250 330 l 250 320 m 250 320 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 250 210 l 250 220 l 260 220 l 260 210 m 260 210 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 210 210 l 210 220 l 220 220 l 220 210 m 220 210 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 150 230 l 150 240 l 160 240 l 160 230 m 160 230 m 300 290 l 300 300 l 310 300 l 310 290 m 310 290 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 280 130 l 280 140 l 290 140 l 290 130 m 290 130 m 290 80 l 290 90 l 300 90 l 300 80 m 300 80 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 320 170 l 320 180 l 330 180 l 330 170 m 330 170 m 240 310 l 240 320 l 250 320 l 250 310 m 250 310 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 220 210 l 220 220 l 230 220 l 230 210 m 230 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 140 90 l 140 100 l 150 100 l 150 90 m 150 90 m 150 120 l 150 130 l 160 130 l 160 120 m 160 120 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 290 170 l 290 180 l 300 180 l 300 170 m 300 170 m 60 290 l 60 300 l 70 300 l 70 290 m 70 290 m 40 130 l 40 140 l 50 140 l 50 130 m 50 130 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 200 60 l 200 70 l 210 70 l 210 60 m 210 60 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 120 180 l 120 190 l 130 190 l 130 180 m 130 180 m 260 60 l 260 70 l 270 70 l 270 60 m 270 60 m 130 190 l 130 200 l 140 200 l 140 190 m 140 190 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 120 240 l 120 250 l 130 250 l 130 240 m 130 240 m 150 50 l 150 60 l 160 60 l 160 50 m 160 50 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 280 270 l 280 280 l 290 280 l 290 270 m 290 270 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 160 140 l 160 150 l 170 150 l 170 140 m 170 140 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 60 200 l 60 210 l 70 210 l 70 200 m 70 200 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 90 190 l 90 200 l 100 200 l 100 190 m 100 190 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 210 80 l 210 90 l 220 90 l 220 80 m 220 80 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 220 70 l 220 80 l 230 80 l 230 70 m 230 70 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 150 320 l 150 330 l 160 330 l 160 320 m 160 320 m 280 80 l 280 90 l 290 90 l 290 80 m 290 80 m 310 210 l 310 220 l 320 220 l 320 210 m 320 210 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 70 280 l 70 290 l 80 290 l 80 280 m 80 280 m 80 230 l 80 240 l 90 240 l 90 230 m 90 230 m 100 290 l 100 300 l 110 300 l 110 290 m 110 290 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 280 150 l 280 160 l 290 160 l 290 150 m 290 150 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 320 210 l 320 220 l 330 220 l 330 210 m 330 210 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 280 220 l 280 230 l 290 230 l 290 220 m 290 220 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 50 140 l 50 150 l 60 150 l 60 140 m 60 140 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 210 50 l 210 60 l 220 60 l 220 50 m 220 50 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 210 310 l 210 320 l 220 320 l 220 310 m 220 310 m 260 40 l 260 50 l 270 50 l 270 40 m 270 40 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 150 70 l 150 80 l 160 80 l 160 70 m 160 70 m 180 160 l 180 170 l 190 170 l 190 160 m 190 160 m 140 240 l 140 250 l 150 250 l 150 240 m 150 240 m 290 240 l 290 250 l 300 250 l 300 240 m 300 240 m 190 130 l 190 140 l 200 140 l 200 130 m 200 130 m 170 130 l 170 140 l 180 140 l 180 130 m 180 130 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 310 300 l 310 310 l 320 310 l 320 300 m 320 300 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 80 260 l 80 270 l 90 270 l 90 260 m 90 260 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 110 150 l 110 160 l 120 160 l 120 150 m 120 150 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 250 240 l 250 250 l 260 250 l 260 240 m 260 240 m 210 320 l 210 330 l 220 330 l 220 320 m 220 320 m 220 310 l 220 320 l 230 320 l 230 310 m 230 310 m 130 280 l 130 290 l 140 290 l 140 280 m 140 280 m 190 260 l 190 270 l 200 270 l 200 260 m 200 260 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 40 290 l 40 300 l 50 300 l 50 290 m 50 290 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 310 230 l 310 240 l 320 240 l 320 230 m 320 230 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 230 90 l 230 100 l 240 100 l 240 90 m 240 90 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 220 220 l 220 230 l 230 230 l 230 220 m 230 220 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 150 270 l 150 280 l 160 280 l 160 270 m 160 270 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 320 230 l 320 240 l 330 240 l 330 230 m 330 230 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 320 130 l 320 140 l 330 140 l 330 130 m 330 130 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 210 180 l 210 190 l 220 190 l 220 180 m 220 180 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 260 190 l 260 200 l 270 200 l 270 190 m 270 190 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 140 50 l 140 60 l 150 60 l 150 50 m 150 50 m 40 270 l 40 280 l 50 280 l 50 270 m 50 270 m 280 240 l 280 250 l 290 250 l 290 240 m 290 240 m 180 150 l 180 160 l 190 160 l 190 150 m 190 150 m 50 260 l 50 270 l 60 270 l 60 260 m 60 260 m 190 60 l 190 70 l 200 70 l 200 60 m 200 60 m 170 180 l 170 190 l 180 190 l 180 180 m 180 180 m 300 260 l 300 270 l 310 270 l 310 260 m 310 260 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 60 190 l 60 200 l 70 200 l 70 190 m 70 190 m 200 100 l 200 110 l
210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 110 160 l 110 170 l 120 170 l 120 160 m 120 160 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 220 80 l 220 90 l 230 90 l 230 80 m 230 80 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 120 280 l 120 290 l 130 290 l 130 280 m 130 280 m 130 250 l 130 260 l 140 260 l 140 250 m 140 250 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 290 300 l 290 310 l 300 310 l 300 300 m 300 300 m 170 110 l 170 120 l 180 120 l 180 110 m 180 110 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 160 320 l 160 330 l 170 330 l 170 320 m 170 320 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 230 280 l 230 290 l 240 290 l 240 280 m 240 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 220 290 l 220 300 l 230 300 l 230 290 m 230 290 m 270 320 l 270 330 l 280 330 l 280 320 m 280 320 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 170 300 l 170 310 l 180 310 l 180 300 m 180 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 310 150 l 310 160 l 320 160 l 320 150 m 320 150 m 250 310 l 250 320 l 260 320 l 260 310 m 260 310 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 210 150 l 210 160 l 220 160 l 220 150 m 220 150 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 140 80 l 140 90 l 150 90 l 150 80 m 150 80 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 150 130 l 150 140 l 160 140 l 160 130 m 160 130 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 190 110 l 190 120 l 200 120 l 200 110 m 200 110 m 60 280 l 60 290 l 70 290 l 70 280 m 70 280 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 320 150 l 320 160 l 330 160 l 330 150 m 330 150 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 210 160 l 210 170 l 220 170 l 220 160 m 220 160 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 220 150 l 220 160 l 230 160 l 230 150 m 230 150 m 260 170 l 260 180 l 270 180 l 270 170 m 270 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 130 220 l 130 230 l 140 230 l 140 220 m 140 220 m 280 260 l 280 270 l 290 270 l 290 260 m 290 260 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 50 240 l 50 250 l 60 250 l 60 240 m 60 240 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 190 160 l 190 170 l 200 170 l 200 160 m 200 160 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 60 230 l 60 240 l 70 240 l 70 230 m 70 230 m 40 190 l 40 200 l 50 200 l 50 190 m 50 190 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 60 170 l 60 180 l 70 180 l 70 170 m 70 170 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 240 260 l 240 270 l 250 270 l 250 260 m 250 260 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 190 250 l 190 260 l 200 260 l 200 250 m 200 250 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 280 70 l 280 80 l 290 80 l 290 70 m 290 70 m 290 60 l 290 70 l 300 70 l 300 60 m 300 60 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 90 130 l 90 140 l 100 140 l 100 130 m 100 130 m 70 290 l 70 300 l 80 300 l 80 290 m 80 290 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 230 300 l 230 310 l 240 310 l 240 300 m 240 300 m 90 230 l 90 240 l 100 240 l 100 230 m 100 230 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 220 270 l 220 280 l 230 280 l 230 270 m 230 270 m 180 310 l 180 320 l 190 320 l 190 310 m 190 310 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 80 290 l 80 300 l 90 300 l 90 290 m 90 290 m 320 180 l 320 190 l 330 190 l 330 180 m 330 180 m 90 320 l 90 330 l 100 330 l 100 320 m 100 320 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 270 170 l 270 180 l 280 180 l 280 170 m 280 170 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 280 210 l 280 220 l 290 220 l 290 210 m 290 210 m 180 80 l 180 90 l 190 90 l 190 80 m 190 80 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 320 90 l 320 100 l 330 100 l 330 90 m 330 90 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 250 160 l 250 170 l 260 170 l 260 160 m 260 160 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 130 200 l 130 210 l 140 210 l 140 200 m 140 200 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 70 160 l 70 170 l 80 170 l 80 160 m 80 160 m 310 310 l 310 320 l 320 320 l 320 310 m 320 310 m 80 190 l 80 200 l 90 200 l 90 190 m 90 190 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 220 40 l 220 50 l 230 50 l 230 40 m 230 40 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 190 270 l 190 280 l 200 280 l 200 270 m 200 270 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 310 200 l 310 210 l 320 210 l 320 200 m 320 200 m 290 40 l 290 50 l 300 50 l 300 40 m 300 40 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 220 250 l 220 260 l 230 260 l 230 250 m 230 250 m 270 280 l 270 290 l 280 290 l 280 280 m 280 280 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 140 290 l 140 300 l 150 300 l 150 290 m 150 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 290 130 l 290 140 l 300 140 l 300 130 m 300 130 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 320 220 l 320 230 l 330 230 l 330 220 m 330 220 m 300 180 l 300 190 l 310 190 l 310 180 m 310 180 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 310 190 l 310 200 l 320 200 l 320 190 m 320 190 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 200 180 l 200 190 l 210 190 l 210 180 m 210 180 m 230 150 l 230 160 l 240 160 l 240 150 m 240 150 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 260 240 l 260 250 l 270 250 l 270 240 m 270 240 m 240 160 l 240 170 l 250 170 l 250 160 m 250 160 m 120 140 l 120 150 l 130 150 l 130 140 m 130 140 m 140 40 l 140 50 l 150 50 l 150 40 m 150 40 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 40 260 l 40 270 l 50 270 l 50 260 m 50 260 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 290 220 l 290 230 l 300 230 l 300 220 m 300 220 m 190 70 l 190 80 l 200 80 l 200 70 m 200 70 m 170 190 l 170 200 l 180 200 l 180 190 m 180 190 m 300 130 l 300 140 l 310 140 l 310 130 m 310 130 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 200 90 l 200 100 l 210 100 l 210 90 m 210 90 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 210 40 l 210 50 l 220 50 l 220 40 m 220 40 m 110 170 l 110 180 l 120 180 l 120 170 m 120 170 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 250 140 l 250 150 l 260 150 l 260 140 m 260 140 m 210 300 l 210 310 l 220 310 l 220 300 m 220 300 m 260 50 l 260 60 l 270 60 l 270 50 m 270 50 m 130 160 l 130 170 l 140 170 l 140 160 m 140 160 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 140 250 l 140 260 l 150 260 l 150 250 m 150 250 m 290 310 l 290 320 l 300 320 l 300 310 m 300 310 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 70 180 l 70 190 l 80 190 l 80 180 m 80 180 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 90 160 l 90 170 l 100 170 l 100 160 m 100 160 m 70 240 l 70 250 l 80 250 l 80 240 m 80 240 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 110 140 l 110 150 l 120 150 l 120 140 m 120 140 m 90 260 l 90 270 l 100 270 l 100 260 m 100 260 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 260 280 l 260 290 l 270 290 l 270 280 m 270 280 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 290 100 l 290 110 l 300 110 l 300 100 m 300 100 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 320 250 l 320 260 l 330 260 l 330 250 m 330 250 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40
扫码加入我们
■
网络翻译爱好者联盟
本字幕由网络兴趣爱好者翻译完成
首发于字幕组网站  ZiMuZu.io
欢迎大家指正纠错  共同进步
翻译：夏棒棒    oops黑吃黑
翻译：Gothicwolf  你的水珠胖次
校对：kayiQQ
时间轴：没人
后期：普罗米修斯
总监：咖啡
■
m 17 5 l 20
0 l 20 15
m 20 15 l 23
5 l 20 0
m 20 20 l 25 5 l 30 5
l 20 30 l 10 5 l 15 5
CN
内容价值网络（Content Value Network）
非常感谢CVN项目方提供CVNT数字货币奖励支持CVN.io
本字幕仅供交流学习之用    所产生的任何纠纷请自行承担
欢迎更多网络翻译爱好者加入我们联盟一起学习交流进步
嗨  索娅  这是辛迪 曼斯菲尔德
Hi, Sawyer. It's Cindy Mansfield
从兰德勒-贝恩打来的电话
from Landler-Bayne calling.
我想和你确认一下本周的面试
I just wanted to confirm your interview this week..
-太好了  -我们还在考虑其他几个候选人
Yes. We are looking at a few other candidates.
但正如你所知  我们对你去年夏天做的工作
But as you know we were all very impressed with the work
印象深刻  我们很看好你
you did last summer and we have a great feeling about you.
我已经给你发了邮件  包含所有的详细信息
I've emailed you all the details
所以我们周三早上九点半
so we will see you on Wednesday at 9:30 a.M.
在我们华盛顿的办公室见  路上注意安全
at our offices in DC Safe drive!
中央学院
现场由州警指挥
State police are on the scene
将车流改道至地面街道
rerouting traffic to surface streets
这会造成一点混乱
that's gonna create a little bit of chaos here
但这就是假日交通
but that's holiday traffic for you.
是的  那堵的可是个噩梦
Yeah, it's a nightmare down there.
不幸的是  正好赶上感恩节周末
Just in time for Thanksgiving weekend, unfortunately.
重新规划路线
Rerouting.
如果你正准备经过那片区域
If you're traveling around that area, your best bet is to stay
你最好能避开主要高速公路
as far away from the highway as possible.
我们全天都会及时将最新的交通情况进行广播
We will keep you informed throughout the day
请持续关注频率12.70 WLUN 肯塔基州
only on 1270 WLUN, Kentucky.
你是想要一个满是硬币的房间
Okay, would you rather have a room full of pennies
还是一叠高达帝国大厦那么高的硬币
or a stack of pennies as high as the Empire State Building?
呃  我想要后面的一大叠
Uh, I think I'd take the big stack.
我会很富有
I'd be rich.
弱爆了
Weak.
重新规划路线至华盛顿特区
Rerouting to Washington, DC.
在30英里处  右转
In 30 miles, turn right.
在500英尺处右转
In 500 feet make a right turn.
前方右转
Make a right turn.
这根本就没路
It's not even a road.
那就在下一个路口右转吧
Guess we're taking the next right.
如果可能  请掉头
Make a U-turn, if possible.
如果可能  请指一条明路
Give me better directions, if possible.
如果可能  请掉头
Make a U-turn, if possible.
向左拐
Turn left.
看到我们了吗
Think they seen us?
真是可以
Okay.
根本就没有任何意义  不停的改变我的路线
This doesn't make any sense. Just reroute me.
这就对了  让手机见鬼去吧
Yes! Suck it, phone!
小姐  你需要帮助吗
You need some help there, miss?
哦  不  我很好  我只是伸伸腿而已
Oh, no. I'm fine. I'm just stretching my legs.
是啊  还有你的地图
Yeah. And your map.
对  我就是在找找方向
Right. I'm just getting my bearings.
是的  我们刚从上面看到了
Yeah, we seen you up there and thought
我们想也许你遇到了些困难
maybe you was having some sort of trouble.
哦  不  我…我只是路过
Oh, no. I'm... I'm just passing through.
你确定没事吗
You sure you're okay?
你看起来有点心烦意乱
You look a little upset.
这些树林  可是个疯狂的地方
And these woods, they can be a crazy place
尤其是当你不熟悉的时候
especially if you ain't familiar.
我想我有点沮丧  你知道吗
I guess I'm a little frustrated, you know.
这些地图不是很有用
These maps aren't super useful.
可不是吗
Ain't that the truth.
所以…就是这样吗
So... so that's it then?
你是路过这里的游客吗
You're just a tourist passing through here?
是啊 好吧 如果你要找方向  x
Yeah? Well shit, if it's directions
我和巴克……
you're looking for, me and Buck..
那是我弟弟巴克
That's my brother Buck there.
我们在这里住了一辈子  所以我们可以把你带到任何地方
We lived here our whole lives. So we can get you most anywhere.
嗯  好吧  嗯  你知道回到64号公路应该往哪走吗
Uh, well, um, do you know the best way back to 64?
I-64
I-64?
还蛮远的诶
That's quite a ways.
你很幸运遇到我们
You're lucky you ran into us.
是啊
Yeah.
因为就只有几条路穿过这些山
'Cause there ain't but a couple roads run through these hills
好吧  你知道  你就只是在这边转圈
and well, you know, you got yourself turned around nowhere.
好吧  看到了吗  就在这里
Alright. See here? Right here.
你走这条路  一直开
You just keep on this way
你会回到高速公路上的  好吗
and you'll make yourself back to the highway, okay.
但你会有走一点重复的路线
But you'll be backtracking quite a bit.
好吧  我想我走的是风景优美的路线
Well, guess I'm taking the scenic route.
是啊  我觉得会的
Yeah. I guess you are.
好吧
Alright.
哦  嘿  嘿  差点忘了  你的地图
Oh, hey, hey! Almost forgot. Your map.
哦  谢谢
Oh, thanks.
天黑之前你哪都到不了
Say, you won't make it anywhere before sundown
我们就住在这条路上面
and we live just up a ways.
那你过来吃晚饭怎么样
So how about you come on over for some dinner?
霍利  我们不应该…哦  他哪儿也去不了
Holli, shouldn't we just... Oh, he ain't going anywhere.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
谢谢  但我真的该走了  所以…
Thanks, but I really should be getting going, so...
不    那个…那个…可不是好主意
No.. That... that... that might not be the best idea.
我是说  你在这里开车迷路了 还是在白天
I mean, you got lost driving around here and that was in broad daylight.
你不会想在天黑后还在外面开车  相信我
And you don't wanna be out here after dark, trust me.
听着  不想冒犯  但你开始让我
Listen, no offense, but you are starting to make me
觉得有点不舒服了
feel very uncomfortable right now.
是吗
Is that a fact?
好吧  听着  我们只是想让你  呃…呃  舒服点
Well, listen, we just want you to, uh... uh, be comfortable.
我们就只想这样
That's all we want.
外面很快就会变很冷
And it's gonna get real cold out here real quick.
你为什么不到我们家来呢
So why don't you just come on back up to our place?
我们喝个一两杯
We'll have a drink or two
也许  你知道  抽点什么
maybe, you know, smoke a little somethin'?
就像一个小聚会
It'd be like a little party.
是啊  来吧  我们一起……
Yeah? Come on, let's all..
该死  婊子砍了我
Goddamn! Bitch cut me!
是的
Yah!
-等一下  亲爱的  -滚开
Now hold on a second, honey. Fuck off!
别让她拿刀
Get that knife away from her!
她要跑掉了
She's gettin' away.
那边  那边
That way. That way.
你确定吗  是啊  来吧
You sure? Yeah. Come on.
可以  我能搞定
Okay. I can figure this out.
是啊
Yeah.
一定会的
Definitely.
倒霉
Shit!
会没事的
It's going to be fine.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's going to be fine.
福特汀县治安官办公室  我是卡兹副警长
Fording County Sheriff's Office, Deputy Katz speaking.
等一下
Hold on.
警长  一号线
Sheriff, line one.
我是欧多伊尔
This is O'Doyle.
嘿  警长
Hey, sheriff
我是查尔斯顿办事处的佩妮
this is Penny from the Charleston office.
我有一份抛锚车辆报告
I have a stranded vehicle report
在那条250县公路上
for that two-five-oh county road.
如果我们能尽快拿到你的注册报告
If we could get your registration report as soon as possible,
因为放假  办公室快关门了
our office is gonna be closed due to the holiday.
佩妮  你能  呃  能等一分钟吗  亲爱的
Penny, could you, uh, could you hold on a minute, honey?
嗯
Mm-hm.
她想要什么
What she want?
呃  只是一辆废弃的车
Uh, just an abandoned car.
呃  这让我想起来了
Uh, it got me thinking.
那个  呃  吊死的家伙  那个西班牙人
That, uh, hanging fella, the Hispanic.
-他叫什么名字  -艾德温 伽罗
What's his name? That's Edwin Garro.
是的  是的  那个叫伽罗的家伙
Yeah, yeah, that Garro fella.
我们应该看看是否有以他的名义登记的车辆
We should see if he had any vehicles registered in his name.
和遗弃车辆报告做对比
Check them against abandon vehicle reports.
你认为这可能是他的车吗
You think this might be his car?
不  不  时间线都不对
No, no, timeline's all wrong
但也许上周有什么发现
but maybe something got picked up last week.
嗯  这可是要查很久的  但要尽职尽责
Uh, it's a long shot, but, you know, due diligence and all.
我马上就去
I'm on it.
你好  佩妮  是的  我很抱歉
Hello, Penny. Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
呃  所以你说是公路250  对吧
Uh, so you say it's up on 250, huh?
嘿
Hey!
好吧
Okay.
嘿  在这里  救命
Hey! Over here! Help!
啊
Ah.
哎哟
Ow.
哎
Phew!
好吧  该死的
Well, dang it!
在你不想说话的时候
You're just as quiet as a cottonmouth
你真是不怎么说话啊
when you wanna be, huh?
你来这里是为了公务  警长
You here on official business, sheriff
或者只是来寒喧吗
or this is just a social call?
我来这里可不是为了寒喧  这你可以放心
I ain't here to take a bunch of lip, you can count on that.
我接到一个关于遗弃车辆的电话
I got a call about an abandoned vehicle
就在拐弯处  在锈溪边上
at the bend, down by Rust Creek.
嗯  正如你所看到的  我们平时都把车子
Well, as you can see, we prefer to abandon our vehicles
放在家里的
right here at home.
好吧  我每天都能看到你和巴克在那条小溪边上晃   所以  呃
Well, I just seen you and Buck tramplin' up from that creek every damn day, so, uh
当我接到州警的电话…
when I get a call from the state police...
州警  这和州里有什么关系
State? What do the staties gotta do with it?
没什么关系   暂时
Nothing, yet.
如果我们看到什么  我会告诉你的
If we seen something I'd tell you
但事实是我们没在那里
but the plain fact is we weren't up there.
尽管你挺胸抬头 气势如虹
Now you can come out here puffing up your chest
但这不会改变事实
all you want, but it don't change the facts.
孩子  你一定觉得我是个绣花枕头吧
Boy, you must think I'm some kind of a prize dummy, huh?
有件事我得告诉你……
Well I got news for you..
放松  警长
Easy, sheriff!
天呐
Jesus!
你有点  有点神经质  拔枪真快
You a bit, you a bit jumpy, Quickdraw.
你受伤了吗
You hurt there?
打猎弄的
Huntin' accident.
哦  你在流血
Oh, you're bleeding right there.
你应该把伤口缝起来
You should get that stitched up.
只是擦伤而已
It's just a scratch.
你在锈溪那边弄的吗
Did you get that scratch up by Rust Creek?
就像我说的…
Like I said..
…我们好几天没去过那里了
...we ain't been up there in days.
好吧  嗯…
Alright, well..
我试过了
I tried.
我尽力了
啊
Ah.
哦  该死
Oh, shit!
哦  一点事都没
Ow. Good as new.
一切都很好
Everything's fine.
会有人看到车的
Somebody will see the car..
他们会知道来这里找我的
They'll find me here.
我在他妈的树林里
I'm in the fucking woods.
哇  天了撸
Whoo! Holy shit!
哈哈哈  太棒了
- Ha-ha-ha! That was amazing!
真是太棒了
That shit was amazing!
你看见那车飞了吗
Did you see that fucker fly?
快点  巴克  我们去看看
Come on, Buck. Let's go check it out!
他妈的
Ho-ly shit.
你看看这个  我们瞄准了一棵该死的橡树
Will you look at this? We bull's-eyed a goddamn oak tree!
他们不会派人来偏离道路这么远的地方
They ain't never gonna send nobody this far off road.
啊  倒霉  现在我们要做的就是找到那个婊子
Ah, shit. Now all we gotta do is find that bitch.
她被刺得很深  霍利
She was cut pretty deep, Holli.
她不会在外面活太久的
She ain't gonna last out here too long.
我们就不能回去吗…
Can't we just go back...
在他们找到尸体之前
Not until they find a body we're gonna have
欧多伊尔和州警在我们屁股后面追着  巴克
O'Doyle and the staties up our asses, Buck.
但是如果他们找到了尸体
But if they find her,
那他们不就会派人漫山遍野搜查了吗
won't they be all over the place anyway?
不  不会漫山遍野
No, not all over.
只会在他们找到尸体的地方
Just around where they find the body.
知道了吗  很好
Get it? Good.
来吧  我们从小溪开始
Come on, we'll start at the creek
沿着小溪走回那条路
work our way back down the road.
妈的  赶紧动起来  这边
Fuck. Move your fat ass. This way.
走吧
Let's go.
来吧  现在注意脚下  巴克
Come on, now watch your steps there, Buck.
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
哦
Oh.
来吧
Come on.
还没干
Ain't even dry.
来吧
Come on.
哦  来吧
Oh, come on.
来吧
Come on.
那里
There.
妈妈
Mom.
呃  如果你你最终能收到 我……
Uh, if you ever get this somehow, I..
…我想让你知道……
...I wanted you to know that..
我…我应该…
...I... I should..
你是谁
Who are you?
哦  我的上帝
Oh, my God.
你在外面干什么
What are you doing out here?
天哪
God!
你他妈的是谁
Who the fuck are you?
那个是给你喝的
You were supposed to drink that.
给我离远点
Stay the hell away from me.
把它放下  把它放下
Put that down. Put that down.
再走一步  我就把这个丢到你他妈的脸上
Take another step and I'll throw this in your fucking face.
-小心点  那是我的…-我认真的  混蛋
Careful now. That's my.. I'm serious, motherfucker!
我会把你他妈的脸烧掉
I'll burn your fucking face off!
卧槽
What the fuck..
嘿  刚刚是怎么回事  嘿
Hey! What was all that about? Hey.
噢  只是警长的事
Oh, just sheriff stuff.
你问过他们那辆SUV的事吗
Did you ask them about that SUV?
嗯  我不知道你在跟进  大SUV案
Um, I didn't know you were taking on "The Big SUV Case."
我.…我只是好奇  你知道  …他们有不在场证明吗
I... I'm just curious. You know, d... did they have an alibi?
不在场证明  证明什么
Alibi for... for what?
证明他们和SUV车辆案件无关
For whatever was going on with that SUV.
尼克  你有这么多空闲时间吗
Nick, do you, do you have such an abundance of free time
为了打发无聊时光
that you need to invent crimes to investigate
还要无中生有吗
just to stave off the boredom?
不  先生  我只是…
No, sir, I just...
如果你再这样的话  我希望有人能解决
Because if you do, I would love someone to tackle
从10月初开始就开始积攒的
"The Case of the Moving Violations Paperwork
搬家违规案件的文书工作
That's Backed Up to Early October."
我知道你想表达什么了  警长
Point taken, sheriff.
但那辆SUV  我是说  你不觉得奇怪吗
But that SUV thing, I mean, doesn't that seem odd to you?
像那样的车  被遗弃   大白天的
A vehicle like that, abandoned, in the middle of the day
找不到司机
no driver in sight?
孩子  你是不是在怀疑我的判断
Are you second guessing me, son?
不  先生  但是…
No, sir. But..
有话直说
Speak plain.
你对待当地人有一套自我法则
You do have a way of treating the locals
其中还带着一定的敬意
with a certain deference.
尼克  你是个好助理
Nick... you're a good deputy.
你是个好人
You're a good man.
我很感谢你的付出
I appreciate your commitment.
有件事我觉得说一次就够了
So I'm just gonna say this one time and I think it oughta be enough.
我是警长
Chief.
你是印第安人
Indian.
摆正自已的位置
Mind your place.
况且  说到普利切特这两个人
And, uh, as far as them Pritcherts are concerned
他们俩上小学的时候就被我抓过
I've been arrestin' them boys since they were in grade school.
他们是很麻烦  这是事实
And they are trouble, that's for sure
但他们没有那种
but they ain't got the brains
违法犯罪的脑子
between the two of 'em to be dangerous.
还有  那辆神秘SUV
And moreover, that mysterious SUV
已经不知道什么时候被挪走了
moved along some time yesterday.
是吗
Oh.
没错
Yeah.
就是说没有油也能开走
Likely just run out of gas then?
也有可能
Likely.
是吗
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
警长   我想给车主打个电话可以吗
Say, sheriff, do you have any objection to me calling the registered owner?
就只是为了把整件事弄清楚
You know, just to put this whole thing to bed?
如果这么做你能比较安心的话  孩子
Uh, if it'll give you some peace of mind, son
那就去吧
go right on ahead.
好的
Right.
吃吧
Eat this.
放弃吧
Uh-uh. Knock it off.
你失血过多
You lost blood.
需要吃点东西
You need to eat.
我需要见医生和警察
I need a hospital and the police.
吃
Eat.
随你便
Suit yourself.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我叫索娅
I'm Sawyer.
- 索耶 斯科特  - 闭嘴好好吃饭
Sawyer Scott. Shut up and eat.
我要去中心大学  是大学生
I go to Centre College. I'm a senior.
我本来是要去华盛顿参加一场面试
I was on my way to DC for a this big job interview
在路上GPS把我给带丢了
and my stupid GPS got me lost.
有两个陌生男人差点抓住我
These two guys jumped me.
我的朋友们肯定很担心我
I'm sure my friends are worried about me.
我爸妈也是
And my parents..
闭嘴
Quiet.
如果你能把我松开
...and if you could just untie me
然后帮我报个警  你就是我的英雄
and take me to the police, you'd be a hero.
嘘
Shh.
我不会跟警察说
I wouldn't even mention the..
你绑我的事
This.
他们可能还会给你些奖金
Might even be a reward.
来人啊  救命  救命
Somebody help me! Somebody help me!
如果他们发现你在这  他们会杀了你
If they find you here they'll kill you.
别出声  不然我也帮不了你
Keep quiet, or I can't help you.
找到他了
There he is.
总是那么严肃  还好吗
Serious as ever. Hello, cuz.
Hollister. Buck.
霍利斯特 巴克
发生什么事了
What happened here?
就是随便逛逛
Aw, just some horseplay. You know.
抱歉我们没有经常来看你
Sorry we ain't been up to visit more.
最近我们遇到点麻烦
Things just been kinda crazy lately.
- 什么事  - 不  没什么
Okay. No, no, it ain't.
我们是一家人  不需要证明  对吗
We're family. No excuse. You know.
- 最后一批货怎么样  - 很不错
So, how'd the last batch go? No problems.
利润跟我们预期的一样吗
And the yield was what we thought it would be?
差不多吧
More or less.
所以下次的行动是  周六
So we should be on target for S... Saturday?
我的麻黄碱等东西快用没了
I get low on sudo and some other stuff.
我们都准备好了
We're all set with that.
我们明天会多带点麻黄碱和氨水
We'll be back up tomorrow with more sudo, ammonia,
还有火柴什么的
matches, whatever.
氨水我还不缺
I'm good on ammonia
但我需要些碱液
but I'm gonna need more lye.
那东西你用的太快了  不是吗
You burned through that shit pretty fast, didn't you?
洛厄尔l想要什么就有什么
Well, hell. What Lowell wants, Lowell gets.
问问他有没有看到那姑娘  霍利
Ask him about the girl, Holli.
对了  那件事
Oh, yeah, about that.
几天前有个女孩在这附近迷路了
Seems some girl went missing up here a couple days ago
欧多伊尔警长
and Sheriff O'Doyle
在追着我们查这件事
he nearly crawled up our ass about it.
你有看到什么吗
I don't suppose you seen anything?
没见过什么女孩
I ain't seen no girl.
好的  你介意我们四处看看吗
Okay. Do you mind if we take a look around?
- 随便  - 是的  确实
- Free country. Yeah. It is at that.
什么都没有
Nothin'.
有什么好奇怪的吗
What's eatin' you?
告诉我  弟弟
Tell me, cousin
自从我们弄了这辆房车之后
how many times me and Buck been up here
我跟巴克来过几次
since we got this trailer set up?
可能十几次吧
Dozen or so.
我们每次来的时候  我是说
And every time we do, uh, I mean
天哪  连巴克都知道
hell, even Buck could tell you.
我们每次来第一件事是做什么
What's the first thing that we do?
进去喝一杯
Go in and have a beer.
没错
Right.
但今天  我们来到你这
But today when we come up here
你却出来见我们
and you step outside to meet us
一直站在这
and stand there the whole time
而且还他妈的下着雨
in the middle of the fucking rain
你他妈的就像个看门狗一样站在这
like you're some kinda goddamn guard dog.
你要说什么
You got something to say?
我想我说的很明白了
I think I'm saying it.
我们从昨天开始在追踪一个女孩
We tracked that girl up here yesterday.
线索在不远的地方中断了
Trail went cold not a hundred yards away.
你藏了什么好东西  是不是
You found yourself some fun, didn't you?
是不是
Didn't you, huh?
我的碱液出了点问题
I had a accident with the lye is all.
里面全是烟
Place is full of fumes.
洛厄尔 洛厄尔
LowellLowell..
你把我当傻子一样骗  你真让我伤心
...it hurts my feelings when you treat me like I'm some kind of goddamn idiot.
那么  不如我们进去看看怎么样
Now, how about we go on inside and have a look.
她不在里面
She ain't in there.
你不该在这
You shouldn't be here.
你弄疼我了
You're hurting me.
总比遇见他们好
Better me than them.
下次我告诉你老实呆着
Next time I tell you to stay put
你就给我老实呆着
you stay put!
- 自杀  - 没错
Suicide? Yeah.
所以你认为这个拉丁美洲人
So you think it's just coincidence
在我们发现墨西哥毒品在美国扩散
that this Hispanic fella from out of town
的时候离开他住地
offed himself right when we got Mexican drugs
只是个巧合吗
flooding the state?
我不能确定
I... I couldn't say.
但是在福特汀镇
But in Fording County
自杀似乎比某个毒品团伙谋杀
suicide seems to make a lot more sense
听起来更有可能一些
than some cartel gang thing.
也许吧  但是我不太相信
Maybe. That doesn't sound right to me.
所以  我们要等验尸官的结果
So, we gonna wait on the coroner.
还有  调度中心的佩妮让我跟进一下
Now also, Penny from Dispatch wanted me to follow up
那辆弃车
on an abandoned vehicle.
那没什么可查的  在同一天也不见了
Oh! That wasn't nothin'. Moved on the same day.
呃  那个
Oh, well, uh..
你有什么要补充的吗  副警长
Well, you got something to add, deputy?
说吧  卡兹
Go on, Katz.
那辆车是帕迪尤卡的一对夫妻注册的
That vehicle was registered to a couple over in Paducah
但是他们把车给了他们的女儿
but they gave it to their daughter.
现在  她
Now, she's over...
你不如直接跳到重点部分吧
Why don't you just get to the part where you tell us the bad news.
司机叫索耶 斯科特
The driver's name is, uh, Sawyer Scott
很明显没人知道她在哪
and apparently nobody seems to know where she is at.
她失踪了吗
She's missing?
她室友说她要回家过
Well, her roommates said that she was going home
感恩节  但是她父母说
for Thanksgiving, but her folks said
她一直在学校
that she was staying on campus.
最后一次有人见到她是什么时候
When was the last time she was seen?
周一早上
Monday morning.
Monday morning?
我刚跟她妈妈通过电话
I... I just got off the phone with the mother
她说给女儿打过电话但她没接
and she said that the girl's not answering her phone.
听着  这都发生在你派你的突击队员
Look, that was before you send out your storm troopers
踏过别人的花坛
start trampling out people's flower beds
砸开别人的家门之前的事
and kicking down their doors.
我们先确定一下她没有
Let's just make sure she's not
在弗吉尼亚海滩或者什么其它地放晕倒吧
passed out in Virginia Beach somewhere.
上帝啊  欧多伊尔
Jesus Christ, O'Doyle
你以为我愿意做你的工作吗
you think I enjoy doing your job for you?
如果不是逼不得已的话
I'm not about to send my men traipsing through the woods
我也不想让我的人在感恩节往树林里走
on Thanksgiving if I don't have to.
但你最好尽快着手调查那个女孩的事
But you better get a line on this girl soon
不然的话警署很快派人坐直升机
or you gonna have state police choppers
带人来搜查这里
blocking out the sun down here.
- 副警长  - 长官
Deputy. Sir.
- 对不起  探长  - 省省吧
Sorry, sheriff... Save it.
有这个失踪女孩的照片吗
We got a picture of this missing girl?
把绳子烧断  你还挺聪明的啊
Pretty clever how you burned through them ropes.
- 那东西是什么  - 碱液
What is that stuff? Lye.
- 是某种酸吗  - 是碱
Is that some kind of acid? Base.
腐蚀的方式有点像酸
Burns like acid.
碱也可以腐蚀
Bases burn too.
那个牛奶  两者可以中和吗
And the milk, that neutralized it?
牛奶的酸度不足以中和碱液
Milk ain't acid enough to neutralize lye.
还需要一些
You'd need something like..
像醋一样的东西来中和它
...like vinegar to neutralize lye.
那你为什么不准备些醋在手边
So why don't you have some vinegar handy?
你知道要是把酸和碱混在一起会发生什么吗
You know what happens when you mix an acid with a base?
会中和
Neutralizes it?
没错  会产生大量的热量
Yeah, with so much heat
灼烧程度比被碱烧更严重
it burn you worse than the lye did.
还以为你上了大学很有文化呢
Thought you were a college girl.
我不是学化学的
I'm not a chemistry major.
所以用牛奶更好
Well, that's why milk's better.
产生的反映更弱一些
Less reaction.
拜你所赐  还是烧的挺疼的
Still burned quite a bit, thank you.
你为什么知道这么多这种事
Why do you know so much about this stuff?
我14岁开始自制冰毒
I've been cooking meth since I was 14 years old.
被烧的多了自然就知道什么东西危险了
You learn real quick what all can burn you.
你知道吗
You know..
要是你放我走  我不会跟他们说你的事
...if you let me go I won't tell them anything.
你说你是要帮我  但你却把我困在这
You say you're trying to help me, but you're holding me here.
我不能放了你
Can't do it.
我发誓我不会说的
I promise I won't tell anyone anything.
让我走吧
If you just let me go.
我们离最近的公路有5英里
We're five miles from the nearest road.
离最近的镇有20英里
Twenty from any kind of town.
我没有车
I got no car.
你这个样子连100尺都走不了
You wouldn't make it a 100 yards the shape you're in.
即使你能走  你遇到的第一个人
And even if you did, the first person you met
十有八九也会把你交给霍利斯特
would like as not hand you right over to Hollister.
屁话
Bullshit.
- 你就是想把我困在这  - 别说了
You just wanna keep me here. Quit it.
你不能永远把我困在这
You can't keep me here forever!
我让你别说了
I said quit it.
你想试试有没有命走出树林  走吧
You wanna try your luck out in them woods, go on.
霍利斯特和巴克这周末要去查尔斯顿
Hollister and Buck are going into Charleston this weekend.
他们会把卡车放在他妈妈家
They'll leave their truck at their mama's house.
我周六会去把车借来
I'll go down on Saturday and I'll borrow it.
然后把你送到个安全的地方
And then I'll take you someplace safe.
离开福特汀县
Out of Fording County.
这个你得帮我一下  真他妈重
I might need some help with this one, heavy as a mother..
上帝啊   欧多伊尔
Jesus Christ! O'Doyle?
我有几个简单的问题问你
I got some plain questions for you
你最好坦白的回答我
and I want some plain answers.
- 是那辆车的事吗  - 去他妈的车
Is this about that car? Hell with the car.
上边派人来问我那个失踪的女孩子的事
Now, I got the  asking about a missing girl!
我们按你说的做了  探长
We did what you told us, sheriff.
小子  你要是按我说的做了
Son, if you'd done what I told you
他们就会在琼斯波罗县
they would've found that girl's body
附近发现她的尸体
somewhere down in Jonesboro County by now.
真不知道你们两个蠢货在想什么
I still don't know what the hell you dimwits were thinking.
我告诉过你  好吗  她在我们掩埋
I told you, okay, she come up on us
那袋鬼东西的时候突然出现
when we was burying that bag of shit.
我们以为她看到什么了
And we thought she seen somethin'!
好啊  她现在确实看到了
Well, she seen something now.
从现在的情况看  她也许已经
At this point, don't it figure she already
冻死在树林里了
out there in them woods froze to death?
她是不是在某个峡谷里死了
It don't matter if she's out there dead in a gully
或者在哪表演唱歌都不重要
or singin' on Bandstand.
见不到人  整个林子
Without a body, these woods
都会遍布警察
is gonna be crawling with state police.
还没人发现她  所以  她很可能死了
Well, she ain't been found, okay? So, she's likely dead.
很有很多鸟去吃腐肉  找到她很容易
The birds will be at her by now. She'll be easier to spot.
等我们把这些运到洛厄尔l那之后
We'll go out again tomorrow
我们再去找
after we run this stuff up to Lowell.
你那表弟怎么样了
How's your cousin doing?
很怪  感觉有点不认识他了
Weird. Like, I don't even know him.
我的意思是  我们的计划没问题吧
What I meant was, are we still on schedule?
你知道那小子只管制毒
Hell, you know that ol' boy don't do nothin' but cook.
这有一大批货  但是周六我们能处理好
Big batch here, but we'll be right by Saturday.
最好能
We'd better be.
早餐吃桃子或者红肠
Breakfast is peaches or bologna.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
剪火柴盒
Cuttin' matchbooks.
- 剪它干嘛  - 做冰毒
What for? Cook meth.
我还以为冰毒是从  某种
I thought meth was made from, like..
氢氧化纳管子里的麻黄素里提炼的
...ephedrine and Drano.
和火柴纸板
And matchbooks.
你为什么要做冰毒
Why are you making meth?
现在大家不都吸海洛因吗
Isn't everyone doing heroin now?
- 人家读到的啦  - 不会煮海洛因
-I read.   -Can't cook heroin.
你要火柴纸板
How many of them do you need?
一大堆
Lots.
你把他们全都剪碎了后再做什么
And what do you do when you have them all cut up?
- 把那些狗屎混进去  - 那狗屎指啥
- Mix that shit in.   - What's that shit?
你为啥这么多屁问题
Why do you ask so many damn questions?
不要介意嘛
Never mind.
人家只是想没准能学点东西呢
Just thought I might learn something.
那么说
So..
你真的是连自己在干啥都不清楚
...you don't really know what you're doing.
你就像那些欧洲的流行乐队
You're like one of those European pop bands
唱着英语歌实际上
that sing in English but don't actually know
一个词的意思都不知道
what any of the lyrics mean.
对一个昨天手还挤在一桶碱液里的
You sure ride high
女孩来说  你真是好了伤疤忘了痛啊
for a girl who jammed her wet hands in a bucketful of lye yesterday.
我不是在埋汰你  人家只是说
I wasn't being condescending. I'm just saying.
你要知道
You know,
他们竟让你做这么复杂的化学实验真奇了
it's amazing they got you doing all this complex chemistry
你甚至不必理解它
and you don't even have to understand it.
你这不叫埋汰啊
That ain't condescending?
那个  我一直在想你那个
So... I've been thinking about your plan
借你卡车的主意
to borrow your truck.
我只是不知道我是否该这里呆那么久
I just don't know I should stay up here for that long.
我的意思是  作为备用计划还可以
I mean, it's okay for a backup plan
但是  你知道  如果你能让我通上电话  那
but, you know, if you can get me to a phone, then...
馊主意
Bad idea.
如果那些人回来了我还在这
If I'm here when those guys come back...
把你留在这里比试着转移你更安全
It's safer to keep you here than to try and move you.
姐才不是那种坐以待毙的人
I'm not really a sit and wait type.
不消你说我都看得出来
You don't say.
听着  我想我能想出一个更主动的法子
Listen, I just think I can come up with a more proactive way to...
嘿  你能把那个大水罐递给我吗
Hey, would you hand me that pitcher right there?
- 为什么这么冷  - 就把它倒这
- Why is it so cold?   - Just pour it in here.
慢慢的
Real slow.
它之所以冷
It's cold
是因为丙酮在里头  它在蒸发
'cause the acetone inside, it's evaporating..
从它接触到的所以东西中吸取能量
...sucking away the energy from what all it's touchin'.
把它和火柴盒混合  把红磷分开
Mix that with the matchbooks, separate the red phosphorous.
然后我将把它和碘混合
Then I'm gonna mix that with iodine
要得到氢碘酸  我需要它来制作冰毒
to get hydroiodic acid, which I need to cook meth.
所以你搞这么半天就为了得到一种成分
So you do all that for just one ingredient?
活就是这么做的
That's the job.
像做一堆科学实验
Like a bunch of little science projects?
混合这种原料  分开那种
Combine this ingredient, separate that one.
是的  还有就每种原料都会杀了你
Yeah, and just about every one of them will kill you.
每一个不是有腐蚀性
Every one of 'em is either corrosive
就是易燃  要么两者兼备
flammable, both.
甲醇  丙酮  乙二醇  丁烷
Methanol, acetone, glycol, butane..
你以为碱液很吓人
You thought that lye was tough.
我们以前用这个做饭
We used to cook with this.
无水氨
Anhydrous ammonia.
目前它是一种会立马灼伤你皮肤的液体
In here it's just a liquid that'll burn your skin right off.
房间一升温  变成毒气
Room temp, it turns into poison gas.
一个火花
One spark..
霍利斯特很快就到
Hollister will be here soon.
哦  天哪  洛厄尔
Oh, God. Lowell.
洛厄尔 洛厄尔
LowellLowell.
LowellLowell. LowellLowell.
L- O-L
L-O-L
明白吗
L-O-L. Get it?
嘿  洛厄尔
Hey, l-o-l!
你在哪
Where you at?
嘿  把它放那儿就行了
Hey. Just put that down there.
嗯  洛厄尔  你在做什么  尽量不要呼吸
Eh, what's cooking, Lowell? Try not to breathe.
- 我们不应该戴口罩吗  - 但我才弄得那个
Shouldn't we get masks? But I just got the one.
最好快速卸货  天了噜
Best unload quick. Jesus Christ.
我以为你会在拖车后面等
Thought you were gonna wait around back of the trailer.
如果霍利斯特来这里怎么办
What if Hollister had come down here?
或者巴克过来
Or Buck?
如果他们从拖车后面过来呢
What if they'd come behind the trailer?
那个嘛  我可以不让他们去的
Well, I could have kept 'em from there.
你得学会蹲着不动
You gotta learn to sit still.
所以  我来的那条路是  是那条路吗
So, that road I came from is, is that way?
那个小镇就在那边
And that little town is that way?
是的  那是布恩
Yeah, that's Boone.
但最近的路是毕舍普
But the nearest road is Bishop
那条路  往东走
that way, to the east.
你打算休息一下吗
You fixing to make a break for it?
你作决定
Your call.
但如果你只是不安  我可以让你工作
But if you're just restless, I can put you to work.
我知道  我知道  我很抱歉
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
我知道我说了什么  但
I know what I said but..
宝贝  这个女孩还在外面
Baby, this girl is still out there
她妈妈打电话来了  并且十分担心
and her mama's been callin', just worried sick.
我们以后还会有很多感恩节
We'll have plenty of other Thanksgivings
但若我们不马上找到这个女孩  她就没有了
but this girl won't if we don't find her soon.
尼克  额  在  警长
Nick! Y... yes, sheriff?
你还在这里做什么  快到晚饭时间了
What are you still doing here? It's almost dinnertime.
嗯  我  我只是  没事  我只是
Well, I... I was just.. It's okay, I'm just..
不  不  该死的
No, no, the hell it is!
这是你们第一次一起过感恩节
It's your first Thanksgiving together.
你回家和你妻子一起吃饭
You go home have dinner with your wife.
- 但如果我不完成  - 这是命令  副警长
- But if I don't finish... - That's an order, deputy.
我想没有你我也可以混一两个小时
I think I can muddle through without you for an hour or two.
给我带碟菜来
Bring me back a plate.
- 去吧  去  去吧  -好  好
- Go! Go, go go!  - Okay. Okay.
谢谢你  警长  宝贝  警长要我回家吃晚饭
Thank you, sheriff. Uh, babe, sheriff's sending me home for dinner.
只是  呃  给我  等我二十分钟
Just, uh, give me, give me 20.
你得大声点
You gotta speak up a bit.
是的  我现在就进我的巡逻车
Yeah, I'm getting in my cruiser right now.
搅打奶油
Whipped cream?
不  宝贝  在感恩节时
No, baby, no stores are gonna be open
是不会有商铺开门的
around here on Thanksgiving.
嗯嗯  谁说你需要鲜奶油南瓜派
Well, who says you need whipped cream with pumpkin pie?
不  我还没有开车
No, I ain't driving all the..
哦  等等  等等  宝贝
Oh, wait. Hang on, babe.
我想我办公室里有些奶油
I think I got some cream in the office.
我说我想我有一些
I said I think I got some c..
珍娜  我的手机快没电了
Jenna, my phone's about to die.
我很快就回家
I'll be home soon.
我也爱你
I love you too.
厌倦了你的借口  霍利斯特
..tired of excuses, Hollister.
你带着那个死妹的尸体来  好吧  或者他
You come up with that fucking girl's body, alright, or so he..
听着  这涉及我该死的退休生活
Listen, this is my goddamn retirement
如果你搞砸了  相信我  你绝对还来不及
and if you screw it up, believe me, you will not live
后悔就死翘翘了
long enough to regret it.
嘿  尼克
Hey, Nick.
嗯  看  我  我能理解
Uh, look, I... I can understand..
只是  你知道  听到了一半的谈话
Just, you know, hearing maybe half of that conversation
那话那可能误会了
it could be misconstrued.
是哦
Right.
得了  别认真嘛
Come on, really?
尼克  看…
Nick, look..
好吧  我们坐着谈
Well, let's just sit down and talk about this.
我从这里站着听得见你讲话  警长
I can hear you just fine from over here, sheriff.
你甚至不给我解释的机会
You're not even gonna give me a chance to explain?
我是说  我
I mean, I..
现在放松
Easy now.
你会有机会解释的
You'll have your chance to explain.
但现在我要走了
But right now I'm walking out of here
你无法阻止我
and you're not stoppin' me.
不用非得这样  尼克
It don't have to be like this, Nick.
对不起  警长
I'm sorry, sheriff.
但不管你卷入了什么
But whatever you're into
你必须为此负责
you're gonna have to answer for it.
你想要一个满是硬币的房间吗
Would you rather have a room full of pennies
或是一堆和帝国大厦一样高的硬币
or a stack of pennies as tall as the Empire State Building?
无所谓了
Never mind.
我宁愿要那堆硬币  什么
I'd rather have the stack. What?
我宁愿要一堆硬币
I'd rather have the stack of pennies.
真高
Real tall.
一堆不多
A stack isn't many.
帝国大厦有100层楼高
The Empire State Building's like a 100 stories high.
比这更适合放在壁橱里
More than that can fit in a closet.
如果我有一叠那么高的硬币的话
If I had a stack of pennies tall as that
这将是你见过的最不可思议的事情
it'd be the most incredible thing you ever saw.
就在这里  蓝峰的中间
Right here, in the middle of the Blue Ridge
硬币连天
pennies to the sky..
人们都会慕名而来
People'd come from miles.
嘿  今天是几号
Hey, what day is it?
星期四
Thursday.
感恩节
Thanksgiving.
我想你会和你的家人在一起  嗯
I guess you'd be with your folks, huh?
事实上  我今年打算甩了他们
Actually, I was ditchin' them this year
为了一次愚蠢的面试
for a stupid job interview.
我知道
I know.
最糟糕的是我甚至没有告诉他们原因
And the worst part is I didn't even tell them why.
如果我没有得到这份工作那我就太尴尬了
I was too embarrassed in case I didn't get the job.
那些到处乱跑啊
All that scrambling around..
我所有的打算啊
...all my plans.
现在有什么关系
What does is matter now?
我妻子过去常说
My wife used to say
人算不如天算
"Man plans, God laughs."
是啊
Yeah.
听起来像是我妈妈会说的话
Sounds like something my mom would say.
总是谈论上帝的计划
Always talking about God's plan.
尽管看起来不怎么样
Sure don't seem like much of one.
当然不怎么样
Sure don't.
埋深一点
Bury him deep.
别把他埋过那条梧桐线
Don't just run him out past that Sycamore Line
弄点泥土在他身上  你明白了吗
and kick some dirt on him. You got it?
那女孩呢  你还有她的钱包吗
What about the girl? You still got her wallet?
嗯哼
Mm-hm.
好吧  我有个主意  怎么避开是非
Alright, I got an idea how to keep the staties
至少在这个周末是这样
off our ass, for the weekend at least.
但我们还是要找到她
But we still gotta find her.
别那样说话  好吗
Do not talk like that, okay?
别担心
Don't worry about it.
我会彻底调查的  好吗
I'm gonna get to the bottom of this, okay?
我肯定  嗯  尼克没事
I'm sure that, uh, Nick is fine.
我相信会有一个完全合理的解释
I'm sure there's a perfectly reasonable explanation..
别挂  我  我只是  我正在做一些事  好吗
Hold on, I... I just, I'm in the middle of something, alright?
呃  詹娜  呃…
Uh, Jenna, uh..
我现在就去处理这件事
I'm gonna go right now and take care of this.
我一知道什么就给你打电话  我保证  好
I will call you soon as I know somethin'. I promise. Okay.
再见
Bye.
耶稣基督
Jesus Christ
我没有时间来对付你的愚蠢
I do not have time for your foolishness
今天早上  道格拉斯
this morning, Douglas.
我的副手失踪了
My deputy is MIA.
他妻子整夜不停地打电话给我
His wife's been calling me non-stop all night.
在她和索耶 斯科特的母亲之间
Between her and Sawyer Scott's mother
我  我走开五分钟不到
I... I cannot go five minutes
就有歇斯底里的电话
without an hysterical phone call.
- 他走了很久  - 他  呃…
He been gone long? He, uh..
他昨天下午离开这里
He left here yesterday afternoon
就没人见过他了
nobody's seen him since.
我是说  我我很担心
I mean, I... I'm concerned.
好消息是我来减轻你的工作量
Well, good news is I'm here to lighten your workload.
我要接管那个失踪的女孩
I'm taking over on that missing girl.
现在  我的团队要到这里来做一个适当的搜索
Now, my team's heading up here now to do a proper search
从锈溪的树林一直到黑脊
of those woods up by Rust Creek all the way through to Blackridge.
好吧  好  这不是秘密  我不喜欢那样
Okay, well, it's no secret I don't like that
但是  呃  我想这是最好的
but, uh, I guess it's for the best.
嗯哼
Mm-hm.
现在有我自己的失踪者要处理
Got my own missing person to deal with now.
好吧  嗯  呃  你给我一分钟
Okay, well, uh, you just give me a minute
我会和你一起出去  我会向你的人汇报
I'll head out with you, I'll debrief your men,
我会把我们所知道的告诉他们
and I'll catch 'em up on what we know.
听着  这不必要  他们已拿到报告了
Look, that ain't gonna be necessary. They got the report.
我让这个女孩的父母从帕迪尤卡过来
I got this girl's parents comin' over from Paducah.
我  很好  一会儿就好
I... it's fine, it'll just be a minute.
去看看尼克的储物柜
Just gonna check Nick's locker here.
看看他是带着自己的便服还是仍穿着制服
See if he took his civvies with him or if he's still in uniform.
真的  欧多伊尔  我们能处理好  好吗
Really, O'Doyle, we can handle it, alright?
我很感激你的提议
I appreciate the offer.
哦  他妈的……
Oh, what the hell..
哦  伙计
Oh, man.
好吧  我要遭天谴的
Well, I'll be goddamned.
虽然我们还没有确定这些联系的实质
Though we have not yet determined the nature of the relationship
我们相信卡兹副警长也参与其中
we do believe that Deputy Katz is involved
在斯科特的失踪中
in Scott's disappearance.
他的警车今天早上在琼斯波罗县被发现
His cruiser was found this morning in Jonesboro County
他很有可能计划逃出本地
so it's a good bet he's fleeing the state.
所以  我们要把搜索范围扩大到西部
So, we're going to extend our search west
直到我们找到这个人
until we find this man.
现在怎么办
Now what?
就是这样
That's it.
20分钟后  你将成为一名正式厨师
In 20 minutes, you'll be an official cook.
这并不难  啊
That ain't so hard. Ah!
你觉得你能静坐20分钟吗
You think you can sit still 20 minutes?
我不知道
I don't know.
嗯  我想我可能是
Well, I think I might be
开始习惯宁静的乡村生活
starting to get used to the quiet country life.
进去
Inside.
呆在后门
Stay by the back door.
如果有麻烦  跑
And if there's trouble... run.
嘿  孩子
Hey there, son.
- 熬毒熬得怎样  - 还成
- How's the cook?   - Fine.
嗯
Hm.
好吧  我只是想过来看看你
Well, I just thought I'd come up here to check on ya.
你也这么做了
And you done it.
离得够近了
That's close enough.
蛤
Wh..
所有  你现在在下命令  是吗
What, you're giving orders now, is that it?
我只是不喜欢任何人打扰我的熬制
I just don't like nobody disturbing my cook's all.
呵呵
Huh.
好吧  让我告诉你一些事情
Well, let me tell you somethin'.
我在这里投资了很多
I got a lot invested in this here.
如果我想进去看看
And, uh, if I wanna go inside and take a look
我要进去看看
what y'all up to, I'm gonna do that.
你不能进去
You ain't.
想想你在跟谁说话
You forget who you're talking to?
我是长官  你是兵
I'm the chief, you're the Indian.
我的地盘
My kitchen..
我说了算
...my rules.
这里也不止你一个制毒的
You know, you ain't the only cook around here.
你最好还是把枪放下  表现得恭敬一点
So, why don't you just set that gun down and make nice?
别逞能了
Don't kid yourself, boy.
在你把枪举起来之前
I could put two in you before you could even
我已经能打死你两次了
get them barrels up above your waist.
不幸的是你站在了一个乙醚桶旁
Lucky for me you're standing next to a drum full of ether.
放在屋里太危险了
Too dangerous to keep inside.
只要有一点铅弹的火花星子打到它
One spark from, say, some buckshot hitting the metal..
你可真是个小机灵鬼
A Pritchert with some brains.
上帝保佑我们
Lord help us all.
行
Alright, well..
做好你的分内工作
You just mind you get this cook done right.
下次我过来
Next time I come up here..
可就不是这么简单了
...I'll know where I stand.
你上司吗
Was that your boss?
听起来好混啊
He sounds like an asshole.
他就像最恐怖的那种蛇
He's the worst kind of snake there is.
会不动声色地咬你
Don't rattle before he bite.
- 看起来不值多少钱  - 会值的
Doesn't look like much. It'll do.
我们还需要多少
How much more do we need?
九 十个吧  可能更多
Nine, ten more cooks.
得花上一天的时间了
That's gonna take all day.
能达到目标就好
Best get to it then.
如果你被问话了  记得就说
But if you get asked, just remember..
护送囚犯接受采访   我知道啦
Escorting a prisoner for interview. I got it.
是嫌疑人
Suspect.
护送嫌疑人接受采访
Escorting a suspect for interview.
别忘了刮胡子
Don't forget to shave.
还有让他坐在后座
And keep him in the back seat.
凭什么让我坐后面
How come I gotta sit in back?
你什么时候见过警察以外的人
On account of when'd you ever see someone that wasn't police
开警车
riding in the front of a police car?
你也不是警察啊
You ain't police.
所以我会给他警服
That's why he's got the uniform.
可恶
Dangit!
记住  在他们给钱之前
Now just remember, don't give them anything
什么都不要给他们
until you get the money.
知道啦
I won't.
要把钱数清楚  知道吗
You count out all that money, alright?
别犯懒  让他们给少了
Don't get lazy and let 'em short you.
你干嘛不亲自去呢
Why don't you just come do the thing yourself
如果这个事情这么重要
if you're so damn nervous then, huh?
我要你干嘛吃的
'Cause that's what I got you for.
别搞砸了  听见没有
So don't screw it up. Alright?
我们只有这一次机会  证明我们的货
We got one chance to show these boys we can compete
不比那些墨西哥人差
with them Mexicans.
洛厄尔做的冰比任何一个墨西哥人都好上千倍
Lowell cooks glass twice as good as any Mexican.
是的  那是我没杀死他的唯一原因
Yeah, well that's the only reason he ain't in the ground.
知道吗  他今天用枪指着我来着
You know, he pulled a shotgun on me today?
我现在还觉得火大呢
It's still burnin' me up.
嗯  他最近是挺奇怪的
Yeah, he's been real touchy lately.
都不找我们去他家喝酒了
Don't even invite us in for a drink no more.
不说了  开干吧
Alright, well, let's do this.
我去里面换下衣服
I'mma go inside and change.
我去坐到后座上
I'mma go sit in the back.
感觉不太环保
Not very green.
但你要是把它倒在地上  就会把地染成红色
Well, if you dump it on the land, it stains the ground red.
前院就会像一个巨大的毒品实验室标志
Like having a big meth lab sign in your front yard.
小溪会把它浣洗干净的
The creek washes it clear away.
等到明天就消失的无影无踪啦
By tomorrow, you'd never know it was here.
都倒干净了吧
So that's it, huh? All done?
是的
Yeah.
我以为你会松一口气呢
I thought you'd be relieved.
我确实松了口气
I am.
你让我离开了  然后呢
So, once you got me out of your hair, then what?
我一直在想你妈妈说的话
I've been thinking about what your mama said.
还有为什么切割火柴
And about how cuttin' up matchbooks
也是制毒的一部分
is part of making meth.
你真是想了很多
You doing a lot of thinking.
我觉得也是
I guess so.
我觉得它们之间是有联系的  你知道吗
I got this idea they're kinda connected, you know?
虽然还没彻底弄明白
I don't got it figured out in my head yet, but..
但是感觉
...it's like..
就像  生活中我们遇到的每一个人
Like, in our life, everyone we meet
都有一种化学反应
is a chemical reaction.
我们会互相影响  改变对方
They change us and we change them.
而被改变后的我们  又继续遇到新的人
'Cause we changed, we can go on and have different
再和他们产生不同的反应
reactions with other people.
我们并不知道每段关系会怎么结束
And we don't always know how it will end up.
这是无法预料的
We don't.
就像火柴   它们也不知道
Like the matchbooks, they don't know
会以何种方式结束
how they're gonna end up.
所以说  不要因为我们没找到解法
But just 'cause we can't see a plan..
就认定这个事情是无解的
...that don't mean there ain't one.
不管怎么说  这让我看事情更乐观了
Anyway, it made me feel a little better about things..
我觉得万事万物皆有联系
...thinking it all fit together somehow.
兄弟
Cousin.
我也很高兴见到你
It's nice to see you too.
你好呀  哈哈哈
Hi, l-o-l.
嘿  等等
Hey.. See, hey, hey!
你对我的着装都没点评价吗
Ain't you gonna say nothin' about my duds, huh?
很适合你
Nice duds.
我明天会把你要的原料带来的
We'll be back tomorrow with your cut.
不用谢
You're welcome.
好了吗
So that's it?
都走了吗
All clear?
我觉得我们应该躲一阵儿
Well, we should probably lay low for a little bit.
我中午去找辆车
I'll go pick up the truck around noon
把你送到州警那里
and drop you off with the state police.
我该怎么跟警察说呢
What'll I tell them?
讲事实就好
Tell 'em the truth.
天黑前我会把这里清理干净的
I'll be cleared out of here by dark.
你要离开这里吗
You're leavin'?
是时候了
It's time.
也待够了
You can only sit still so long.
而且  树林里耳目太多了
Besides, there's too many ghosts in these woods.
那这个应该可以还给你了
I guess I can give this back now.
你留着吧
Keep it.
就当是纪念品吧  拿回去
A conversation piece, for all the friends
给你将来在华盛顿认识的朋友看看
you're gonna make in DC.
我不认为他们会感兴趣
Yeah, I'm not so sure that they're gonna..
老狗比
You old dog.
这我就都明白了
This explains everything!
你明明可以直接告诉我的呀
Well, you could've just told me.
- 他不想分享呢  - 他也用不着分享
He didn't want to share. And he shouldn't have to.
如果是我们先遇到她呢
So what if we seen her first?
我一点都不在乎
That don't mean nothin' to me
我兄弟洛厄尔的幸福
when it comes to Cousin Lowell's happiness.
别过来  你给我待在原地 洛厄尔
N... now, now, now you just, you just hold on there, Lowell.
你最近的表现让我觉得你靠不住
You proven to be pretty untrustworthy lately
所以我觉得这事
and I don't think we can leave it up to you
不能由着你了
to do the right thing here.
这个小姑娘
So this little lady..
我们要带走了
...is just gonna have to come with us now.
坐会儿吧  霍利
Take a seat, Holli.
没时间跟你掰扯了  洛厄尔
We ain't got time to be havin' this conversation, Lowell.
时间总能挤出来
Make time.
不会耽误太久的
Won't take long.
索娅  甜心
Sawyer, honey..
去给我热杯咖啡吧
...you mind heating me up a cup of that coffee?
没关系的
It's okay.
去拿咖啡吧
Just fetch the coffee.
我就不该知道这些的
I swear I should've known.
明明在那个见鬼的树林里一起经历了那么多
We been all through these goddamn woods.
事情是这样的
Here's the thing..
我知道应该做什么
...I know what has to get done.
而且我会照做
And I'll take care of it..
以我自己的节奏
...in my time.
但是现在
But for now..
能不能就让我稍微享受一下
...would you just let me have some fun?
你也看见了  她很听话
I mean, you see how trained I got her, don't you?
好了  宝贝
That's it, baby.
现在  过来  坐在我腿上
Now, get over here and sit on my knee.
天哪
Goddamn!
你确实有
You sure do got some things
两把刷子
to teach me, boy.
这事儿要是我说了算的话
And the thing is, if it was up to me...
- 霍利  - 等会儿  巴克
Holli? H... hang on, Buck.
我觉得有点不对劲
I think there's something wrong...
稍等一下  虽然我也觉得这样很好
Hang on a second, the thing is though
但这真不是我能决定的事
it ain't just up to me..
但是  霍利  微波炉
But, Holli, the microwave..
加油
Come on!
快点
Please!
我动不了
I can't.
你还记得毕舍普路在哪儿吗
You remember Bishop's Road?
我不能
I can't..
你一定能逃出去的
You're gonna be okay.
快跑
Run!
放松
Easy now.
别做傻事
Don't do nothin' stupid.
你是我们家族的耻辱
Yous about all the stupid this family needs.
你做这些傻事
Why'd you go and do all this?
就为了一个女孩
For some girl?
无所谓了
What does it matter?
都结束了
It's done.
警长
Sheriff.
该死的洛厄尔
Jesus! That fucking Lowell.
那个女孩一直都在这儿
She was here the whole goddamn time.
- 毒品呢  - 在路边的警车上
Is the meth.. The cruiser, down the way.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
那个女孩跑了  欧多伊尔
That girl run off, O'Doyle.
从树林里走的
Through them woods
要去毕舍普路
headed toward Bishop's Road.
我去追她
I'mma go after her.
- 你沿路包抄  - 好
You circle around the road. Okay.
我会把她赶到你那里
And I'll flush her out to you.
好  好
Yeah, yeah, that's, uh..
是个好主意
...good thinkin' there.
别忘了你的枪
Don't forget your gun there.
哦对
Right.
妈的
Fuck!
赶紧啊  捡起来
Go on, pick it up.
快点
Come on, boy.
欧多伊尔
O'Doyle
你不能这样
You can't.
我们是一伙的
We're partners.
继续啊
Go ahead.
我不
I won't.
我不会这么做的
I won't, I won't do it.
如果我没有武器你就不能开枪
You can't shoot me if I ain't armed.
你觉得在此情此景下
You think I'm concerned with the forensics
有人会在乎你是怎么死的吗
on a known felon shot outside a burning meth house?
孩子  我不想让你觉得我一点反抗的机会都没给你
Son, I just wanted you to feel like you had a fighting chance.
但你确实没有
You didn't.
所以你说
So you're saying..
这个洛厄尔 普利切特
...this Lowell Pritchert guy..
把你留下了
...was holding you?
不  不是留下我  是让我躲起来了
No, not holding me. Hiding me.
哦好  为了让那些追你的人
Oh, okay, from, uh, from these other fellas
找不到你
that was after you.
你为什么不多叫些人来
Why aren't you calling this in?
他可能还活着
He could still be alive.
冷静点  小姑娘
Hold on now there, miss.
在我弄清楚事情经过前
No sense in callin' anything in
还不能叫人来
until I get all the facts.
所以你说还有一些人
So these other fellas, uh..
是两个人吗
...was it just the two of them?
巴克和霍利斯特
Buck and Hollister.
他俩在一个人手底下干活  我不知道是谁
They all work for somebody else but I never saw him.
你起码该叫个救护车
Shouldn't you at least call an ambulance
或者支援什么的吧
or back-up or somethin'?
事情是这样的
Well, now, here's the deal
你得习惯我做事的风格
you're just gonna have to trust my way of doin' things
毕竟方圆十里
'cause around here..
我是长官
Well, I'm the chief..
你们是兵
...you're the Indian.
所以他们的头儿你从来没见过是吧
So, this third guy, you never saw him?
有他的名字吗
Did you get a name?
没有
No.
声音呢
A voice?
- 什么  - 他的声音
Um, what? A voice?
你有听过他讲话吗  声音是怎样的
Did you hear him? What his voice sound like?
说不清
I don't know, just..
就是很普通的声音吧
...just normal, just a normal voice.
这么说听到他的声音你也认不出他咯
Hmm. So you wouldn't recognize him if you heard him again.
是的
No.
我听不出来的
I definitely wouldn't know.
剩下的路我们得下车步行了
I think we're gonna walk the rest of the way.
下车吧
Come on now.
再往前走一点
Just go on down a little further there..
到河旁边
...down by the water.
这条河叫锈溪
They call this Rust Creek..
因为山上的土
...because of all the clay deposits up the hill.
把这条河染成了红色
Turned the water red.
在我出生前山上的土就被挖空了
And they mined up all the clay before I was born.
但是名字也没再改了
That name stuck though.
继续往前
Let's go on now.
好
Okay.
请不要杀我
You don't have to do this.
往水里走
In the water.
字幕 oldenBeard  时轴  oldenBeard
Subtitles by explosiveskull Sync by GoldenBeard